All
Speaker 1: right, guys, so we previously told you that there is a journalist, an accomplished journalist named Yoichi Clark Shimatsu, formerly the editor of the Japan Times, who made some stunning claims about Kamala Harris and her late mother, Shamla Goplin. As a graduate of Berkeley University, Clark, as he prefers to be called, ran in the same circles as them, and he claims...
Speaker 1: Kamala's mother was a part of the CIA's MKUltra program, a psychopathic, sadistic program that ran throughout the 60s, probably is still running today, in which Americans and even government agents alike were drugged and sometimes murdered with the aim of brainwashing the masses. Clark also claims, rather stunningly, that Kamala Harris was previously married to a wealthy Canadian, a marriage which her connections to the deep state
have
Speaker 1: gone through great pains to delete from public record. So is he telling the truth? Well, I'll let you decide because today we welcome him onto the show. Welcome back to Candace.
Speaker 2: okay yoichi clark it is an honor to have you
Speaker 3: join the show today i'm just going to let guests
Speaker 4: know that you are joining by audio because you are in a very remote area but welcome to the candace show
Well,
Speaker 5: thank you very much. Very glad. You know, I'm a rather minor character in this border trauma right now,
Speaker 6: and I'm afraid communications where I am are really, they've been tampered with because of the border situation. You know, it's just, it's terrible down
there.
Speaker 7: Well, you might be a minor character down there, but you're definitely a major character on my
podcast
Speaker 3: right now. You know, we have just been crawling through Kamala's background and her history. I'm sure you're very aware of that. And
Speaker 4: we did come across your piece, which was quite fascinating for a lot of reasons. You know, you had mentioned a previous marriage that Kamala had. You had mentioned the MKUltra program. I would like to just start with Kamala's mother and speak about the MK Ultra program because it's actually a
Speaker 4: program that I have been speaking about at length on the podcast this year that I've been asking Americans and the world to really familiarize themselves with. So can you just let us know how it is that you are familiar with Shamala Goplin, Kamala's mother's work, and what it is that you know about her, please?
Speaker 8: Well, I'm sort of a contemporary of theirs in the Berkeley area. I worked at a news service
Speaker 6: in San Francisco, the Pacific News Service. And so very familiar with the characters there, where she lived, of the foreign student population at Berkeley. And I did attend the graduate school of journalism at Berkeley. So this is all familiar ground for me, Kamala.
Speaker 6: was a prosecutor later when, you know, she was behind the incarceration of like hundreds and probably thousands of young black, there was young kids, but you have to understand the situation then, the older guys who were running the drug trade for the country,
Speaker 6: cartel at the schools they were forcibly recruit these young guys and she was just slamming them
in a
Speaker 6: prison they were just horrible and that's one reason why a lot of black men refused to vote for her now she you know just that one-sided treatment while she let all the major cartel uh figures walk or just warned them get out of here uh because the cops are trying to arrest you so she was in the thick of it she was the girlfriend of willie brown
Speaker 6: who was a lawyer. He had a law office for the cartel. Literally, he became mayor and a state senator. But she was just in the dirty business. And one of my best friends and protege,
Speaker 9: Jeff Adachi, died mysteriously. Yes.
Speaker 2: Let's actually speak about that. So you have a young friend and your protege named Jeff Adachi. And the
Speaker 4: first time that I had come across his name was in your piece. And I did do a little bit of research. And it is a fact that he did die rather mysterious
Speaker 4: And I think it would be fair to say that he was a contender of Willie Brown's office. Willie Brown was running somebody against him. Definitely made enemies, I would say, of the Democrat elite
Speaker 3: class in San Francisco. So could you just inform my readers a little bit more about Jeff Adachi?
Speaker 5: The thing is, he was at Bolt Hall as a contemporary of Kamalus. Kamalus, he was a straight-A student,
Speaker 6: and they were going to kick her out because her grades were so bad, and they didn't think she'd make it in the law. She's never been a good speaker. And he was appointed
Speaker 10: to be her tutor and got her through Bolt to get her degree. Later on, she was hired to be public prosecutor,
Speaker 10: And strangely enough, he was a public
Speaker 6: defender, and he set up this huge program in which a lot of people really – a lot of parents in the Western Edition and in the Fillmore, those of the black districts, were really enthusiastic because he was getting the kids out of prison. These were really hardcore prisons, and getting them into special ed programs, educational programs, work-study programs, and straightening them out, and hundreds of kids, and so –
Speaker 6: the community was overjoyed and then um one day he was found dead in his apartment and they made all kinds of things that oh he had this affair with his russian woman as if uh she had killed him but no she was just a visitor in town he had gone over a visitor and chat with her and then the uh autopsy was also the first one said oh he was uh died
Speaker 10: of all these drugs the second autopsy showed him to be clean
Speaker 11: So this
Speaker 10: was just a major, I hate to use the word conspiracy, but that was a
Speaker 6: conspiracy about his murder to eliminate the guy who was, who knew too much about Kamala, had opposed her treatment of young people.
And
Speaker 6: they awed him, basically.
Speaker 4: Well, you're on the right program to talk about conspiracies. I'll tell you that for free. One of the things that I've noted is that it does seem that part of this, if you want to call it a cabal, call it a mafia, one thing that they understand is to make sure that they control the medical examiner's office.
And I
Speaker 4: don't think that there's any person in the entire world who would doubt that now, especially following COVID, that medical examiner offices are polluted with politics. And yes, if you're listening to this,
you shouldn't
Speaker 4: look into the Jeff Adachi story. There's no question. You have a young person who has his entire life ahead of him. He dies rather suspiciously. And then the media starts throwing out all of these theories, which is what they tend to do. They create a bunch of theories that it confuses the masses and they look everywhere, but where they should be looking. Now, I did not realize that he had helped Kamala in
Speaker 12: the past. I did not realize that they had a relationship. You
Speaker 13: would not have gone into law without his guidance and really
Speaker 14: attention. And it took a lot of time away.
Speaker 14: from him he was not a rich person his father was an automobile mechanic uh he worked his way through school i mean and he was and as a spring-laid suit that's just amazing really nice kid he helped me out a lot with uh the uh southeast asian refugees following the vietnam war when they were banned from coming to the u.s and i was dealing with a flood of them and needed some legal help because
Speaker 14: And Jeff just stepped right forward, took care of it and a really great kid. He didn't drink, didn't smoke, he was a really clean kid. You know, we would go to bars in Japantown, good singer at karaoke, but he didn't drink a drop. He was just a totally nice kid, all American.
And
Speaker 4: just what was the year, by the way, in which he passed?
Speaker 4: or around about i
Speaker 14: think uh he died in early 90s i was by then in japan i had been hired after the uh sat jisco earthquake uh paper in japan so i took off and i didn't hear about his death from my friends you know because they were so tied up with it and it was only much later that i found i heard i heard it yeah i said what happened to jeff and he says oh didn't you hear you know, he died, you know, and then... What is it? It was a funny shot to me, and there was no...
Speaker 14: nothing I can do it at the beginning. So it took me a long time to chesh up with Kamala on this one.
Speaker 15: Okay. So what is it about Kamala
Speaker 4: that Jeff Adachi knew that you believe would have created some conflict for her? The
Speaker 16: cartel connection. Yeah. Yeah. It is. Yeah.
Speaker 14: Yeah. It wasn't mafia. Yeah. It wasn't conspiracy. It was a cartel. She was an agent of the cartel. And I know other stories, too, about members of that. When San
Speaker 17: Francisco was very
Speaker 17: Close circles, not a large city.
Speaker 18: Right. We heard the same thing from Judge. No one knew
Speaker 17: everything else, and no one really wanted to talk except me. I worked at the
Speaker 14: Pacific News Service, and I broke these stories, but even they were scared to take on the cartel.
Speaker 4: Very interesting. And, you know, I did recently speak to Judge Joe Brown and he kind of intimated the same that she was definitely involved in a lot of dirty politicking and especially Willie Brown as well. And you mentioned Willie Brown in your piece and his connection, which you allegedly had to the cartel.
Speaker 1: Could you expand on that, please?
Yeah,
Speaker 17: well, he was from West Texas. There's a lot of, in California, a lot of
Speaker 14: immigrants from West Texas, you know, when the cattle industry wasn't, the ranching industry wasn't doing well, they migrated to West. He got a law degree, I believe in San Francisco. And,
yeah.
Speaker 17: His contact with the cartel was very, very early on. They probably helped him get his law degree. I remember one time, he knew me. We were going to a public event. It was sort of like a carnival. There was going to be some speeches at. And I was walking toward that with my girlfriend. And he comes right behind me, grabs me by the left arm, and squeezes my arm as hard as he can. But you have to understand,
Speaker 17: I used to be a steel work welder, I worked all kinds of jobs earlier in my life, so I was tough as nails, and once he felt my muscles flexing, he opened his hand up and just walked past me, past as hell, sort of in humiliation, you know, that he couldn't intimidate me. Wow. That's the kind of guy he was.
Speaker 19: Wow, unbelievable, you hear these stories.
He
Speaker 17: was a very threatening fellow.
Speaker 17: And he knows me when I talked about the-- another girlfriend of him is London Breen. She's a man of San Francisco. And the first thing she does for homeless people as a walking wagon is give a pack of syringes and a bottle of
Speaker 20: heroin to inject. - Wow.
- It's not a joke.
Speaker 20: And so working on
Speaker 15: behalf
Speaker 4: of the cartel and we heard from Judge Joe Brown last week also that while she was in power in San Francisco, that she worked to help George Soros essentially legal commit legal theft by protecting one of his companies. And so we're hearing over and over again that essentially she was given power to.
Speaker 4: to make sure that the elites are allowed to continue these various
Speaker 21: illegal trades that they're participating in. And you seem to confirm that. I do want to...
Speaker 22: San Francisco
Speaker 23: was run by
Speaker 10: basically the Jewish mafia. You know, Dianne Feinstein, she was born a Catholic and went to Catholic girls school. But she married a Jewish guy and then just flipped over and then...
Speaker 10: And the Jews were behind the drug
Speaker 23: industry there. I remember visiting the hollow one because a friend told me, oh, we got to go over there and visit this guy.
And we
Speaker 23: went there and he was the biggest dope dealer, distributor in
Speaker 24: San Francisco. He ran a garage, a big public garage in the middle of the city where it was a lot of money laundering. And he was there right there, seeing this about it, counting the cash at his little desk while his wife jumped on me and started rubbing her boobs on me.
Speaker 24: place you know
Speaker 17: who was this uh i forget his name he was uh he was the major money uh launderer for the cartel and he the laundry
Speaker 24: was this
huge public
Speaker 24: garage that everyone in san francisco to park there because a very bad city had to use just like this like six-story garage you know and then uh he lived on
boat hill
Speaker 24: there in a big mansion and i was just invited there by a friend and uh you know we were smoking some weed and he was saying you know this is the greatest era in american history because the heroes like uh what's the name the head of microsoft the head of microsoft
uh
Speaker 25: bill gates
Bill
Speaker 17: Gates. Yeah, he's a giant of American industry. And I think this guy's out of his mind. He's smoking too much of the product that he's been selling. He was very core to the whole Jewish community.
Speaker 17: lawyers, but more important, the real estate industry. 'Cause that's why they had all the young boys arrested. They clear out the Western edition 'cause they wanna put up nice, cute little apartments and cottages for the gays coming in from all over the country. 'Cause they figured it was all, most of it are from rich families. They live like
Speaker 24: by two hours to a building, share quarters.
And
Speaker 24: they're going to die of AIDS, you know, within the next
Speaker 17: six years. So the house will be up for real estate again.
Speaker 27: Wow. It's
Speaker 17: really cynical. It's like this is like a Dracula movie. You know, it's something out of this world. And this is America's
Speaker 28: most liberal city. All
Speaker 29: right, guys, the media has dubbed this the abortion election. We have to stand up to this evil.
Speaker 1: When you join forces with Preborn, the largest pro-life organization in the nation, you are protecting the greatest victims in our society, babies in their mother's wombs. Preborn's network of clinics are positioned in the highest abortion areas in the nation, and they have rescued over 300,000 babies. When a woman considering abortion searches to end her baby's life, Preborn is there. Preborn gives these women in need a free ultrasound. The power of hearing a heartbeat on an ultrasound combined with God's love doubles a baby's chance at life.
One
Speaker 1: ultrasound costs just $28, and up to five ultrasounds are $140. Any gift will help their cause, and all gifts are tax-deductible. To donate securely, just dial pound 250 and say the keyword baby. Again, that's pound 250 baby. Or you can go to preborn.com slash Candice. That's preborn.com slash Candice. Yeah, and it's just, like I said, it's stunning because we had Judge Joe Brown on
Speaker 4: here, and he's confirming all of the same things. You know, he was speaking about Martin Luther King's assassination.
And he
Speaker 4: was speaking
Speaker 4: about, you know, how the government had a hand in that. And it is, I think, for a lot of people who about over a million people, I think a million and a half people have watched that episode. And they said, I feel like I'm learning American history for the first time, because you learn in your textbooks that everything was just above board. And America has just been this great country. And, you know, it's very...
Speaker 4: Stunning to hear from people who grew up in these various cities about, you know, mafia related crimes talking about drugs talking about the corruption of Kamala Harris and how she was in the weeds on this and quite terrifying knowing that she is trying to be elected as the president of the United States. I do want to shift gears and talk about her mother because I was quite stunned.
Speaker 4: by your assertion that she was involved in the MKUltra program. And yet that to me seemed to be the only thing that made sense because she seemed to be sort of infiltrating the civil rights movement. And I'm going, what is this alleged brilliant scientist doing, you know, constantly involving herself in civil rights programs?
Speaker 4: protests and making friends with these individuals and because i'm well read on the mk ultra program i i recognize
Speaker 3: the connection there can you speak about what she did or what what you are alleging she did yeah well the
first
Speaker 10: but the first little bit the first place i understand that the poland clan they were
Speaker 24: like clerks uh uh judges spies
Speaker 24: for the british uh when india was a british colony and uh miscobalan was born when it was still a british colony
so uh
Speaker 24: the rest of the country was up in arms fighting against the british but they were very very loyal to the british intelligence service and police service in india so this is how they all got ahead like uh catering to
to
Speaker 24: the british and that enabled uh uh shayamala gopalan uh when she was uh after she got her degree in matras india to you know uc berkeley
Speaker 30: which was is not the cheapest school in the universe north california a really inexpensive place to go it's the most expensive place i know i went through there it was very expensive
Speaker 31: there uh she got she worked at the monkey lab there she was into uh
Speaker 31: It's a real strange
Speaker 32: combination of psychology and Simian studies and zoology, okay? And she was an expert, you know, training monkeys and all that. And Madras is an area, her hometown, where there's a lot of monkeys running around the Hindu temples and all that. And so she's very familiar and very good with them.
And
Speaker 33: she developed a theory.
Speaker 34: And this was a time of King Goodall. There's a huge boom of women who
Speaker 32: work with apes. There were eight programs set up all across the United States and England and Europe on the excitement of the Goodall story, on news stories.
I'm
Speaker 32: good all we're treating monkey children as sort of like human children and getting some very, very good responses at obtaining them.
So
Speaker 34: she was of that school. Now, what happened while she was at UC Berkeley, after she got her degree, she moved out of Berkeley and took her two kids
Speaker 9: and divorced her husband, this guy Harris, Donald Harris, who was, well, at the time he was in biology.
then he
Speaker 9: went into
Speaker 9: law, divorced them, and moved to San Francisco and did nothing for two years. She waited two years while her application was in to a hospital in Montreal. So this was the Jewish hospital
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): in Montreal, okay, that she applied to.
Speaker 25: Yes, that's where she eventually did work.
Yeah,
Speaker 25: she was eventually employed there
Speaker 9: process because they had to check all your background, everything, every little detail about her. And this is because the very famous psychiatrist who really got the MK Ultra program going, Ewan Cameron, Ewan Cameron, he was a Scottish guy, a pedophile, and he was a torturer. You know, he used all sorts of drugs on victims of that program. He passed away.
And
Speaker 9: there was like an eight, six, about seven to eight year hiatus where his program was shut down because there was no one in charge. And they had to move the program because Congress, there was a secret, not so secret, there was an investigation in Congress about MKUltra. So the heat was on the Canadians. The UN cameras lab was in Montreal.
Speaker 9: uh so uh there was the heat was on the canadians to fess up so they shut that lab down uh they as a allen is an infamous allen lab and then they wanted to set up another center also connected to
Speaker 36: the university of of uh midview university there Montreal had to have that certification uh and
in the
Speaker 36: meanwhile they were trying to find the new director to take over
Speaker 37: from them And then she finally got the call.
They
Speaker 37: brought her over, they
Speaker 9: set her up for another one at the Jewish hospital, annexed,
Speaker 36: and she took charge of the, not only a monkey lap, she took charge of the patient care ward.
It
Speaker 36: was a small patient care work, because that hospital, Jewish Memorial, had a psychiatric clinic also. So she worked as a psychiatrist there in a very small division, which
Speaker 9: became the Center for the Revived MK Ultra program.
Speaker 2: Okay, so this is, I'm just going to ask a question here.
So I
Speaker 2: did not realize that the person who started the program
Speaker 4: was a psychologist named Cameroon. I was under the impression that the person
Speaker 4: - You
and Cameron. - You
Speaker 4: and Cameron.
Speaker 39: Yeah, I was under the impression that it was Dr. Sidney Gottlieb who--
Speaker 40: - No, no, no, no. - Okay. - Sidney Gottlieb was a golfer, he was applied. He wasn't into research.
Speaker 41: - Okay.
Speaker 36: - He just applied everything Cameron had developed.
Speaker 36: - Use of drugs, hypnotism,
you know,
Speaker 36: light deprivation, all of those nasty techniques to destroy a human willpower. - Wow, wow. - To capture their brain.
Speaker 36: Gottlieb is a famous one, and everyone thinks MKUltra was basically the American technology. No, it came out of London. It came out of the Tavistock Institute of Sigmund Freud.
Speaker 3: Yes. World War II. I am just so shocked that you are bringing this up
Speaker 4: because I got into a lot of trouble with the media for discussing Sigmund Freud at length, and I've been doing it on this podcast. It's super important for people to learn the truth about him, that he was a person who created a method of psychology, essentially, to gaslight people who were, in fact,
Speaker 4: um, being molested by their own parents, you know, and that he, that's why he was obsessed with children and sex. And it's shocking that we learned that he's a hero in psychology and it's just very important for people to learn the truth about him because psychology is then his family is then what bred propaganda. That would be the Bernays family and
Speaker 39: Edward Bernays. And, um, you are correct. This, this all fits right into the MKUltra
Speaker 4: program, which was designed to see how you could break down someone's will, how you could hypnotize them, uh,
We
Speaker 4: spoke at length on this show about how the Charles Manson murders, that was actually the CIA and everything that the public thinks they know about that. Same areas you're talking about, San Francisco, California. These are federal agents that were obsessed with learning how to hypnotize the public, how to destroy people's will. And a big part of that was molestation. And Sigmund Freud had, in fact, written pieces about how molesting someone when they are a child
Speaker 4: sodomizing. They were interested in exploring how they could create psychopaths. That's also another element of these programs and psychology. And I think it's hard for people to come to terms with how evil that is. And you're now saying that Shamala got the call and she then took a part in this program of testing...
Speaker 43: Yeah, military
Speaker 9: intelligence created this brainwashing techniques. They developed obviously massively during World War II because they tried to use that against the enemy, German allies and so on, the German enemy, and also against reluctant allies.
Speaker 9: mind control techniques. But after the war, I think it was in the late 1947 or 1946, between 1946 and 1948, the British military created the Tavistock Institute, which is on Tavistock Square in London. Sigmund Freud himself flew
Speaker 36: over from Switzerland to London to cut the opening ribbon.
And
Speaker 36: then he assigned one of his sons to be the
Speaker 44: director of the place. He was right behind. He was the main psychiatrist in his family. Yes,
Speaker 15: I'm familiar with Tavistock. There is also
Speaker 4: some indication that even the Beatles and music has come out of Tavistock
Speaker 1: University and how it could transform. Yeah. Modifying human behavior.
That
Speaker 40: their craziest album is all about mind control.
Speaker 1: Right. That's exactly right.
So
Speaker 34: then what happens
is,
Speaker 34: And as the, this came under
Speaker 9: some parliamentary review, there were some complaints, so they decided to move the core of the program to Montreal for a British colony, close to the United States, for good for contact.
And
Speaker 9: sort of out of the way,
Speaker 36: who would ever suspect that this dark genius program is going on in beautiful, wonderful, forested Canada, right? Wow. And the French part of Canada, too. Who would ever suspect that? And they could use the French as guinea
Speaker 9: pigs, right?
Speaker 46: Yeah. Now,
when
Speaker 9: Shyamala came in, there was a concern about...
Speaker 9: about uh the british colonies and so shamala was more adapting this to the colonial subjects not just the caucasian people and so they sent over a british disinfo agent hardy al baines uh he was a character i've actually been to one of his speech the case was very intelligent perfect english
Speaker 9: But obviously, there was something touched about his brain. And then he created the Communist Party Marxist-Leninist, okay, of Canada, okay? It's the only Communist Party in Canada. And a really evil character, okay?
And the
Speaker 9: patients that Sharmala was producing for him, very convenient, both Indians. He was a Sikh.
Speaker 9: but very independent of the Sikh movement. He was not part of the Sikh liberation movement. Him and Sharmala were called, we call them conspirators, I guess you call them. She would give him her patients, the young ones, especially when they were focusing on younger people. They thought older people were not great subjects for this program. You use young guys out of orphanages, out of prisons, and so on, to the detention.
She was like, "Oh, no.
Speaker 9: He put them with a hearty out, and he did this thing called the living statues, okay? I saw one. I think it was a July 4th weekend. I had a lot of jobs in New York, but July 4th was my rare three-day, four-day holiday. I took off with a bunch of friends, and one Canadian guy wanted to go home. We drove up there all night, and in the morning as we approached Montreal,
We
Speaker 9: saw the human statues, you know, on the road. So we slowed down and stopped, got out. My friends were pretty rowdy
Speaker 31: and been drinking beer all night. Walked up to these guys, the guys and women, you know, girls, guys and girls. They were all in these revolutionary poses, you know, like Russian revolutionaries, some with their fists up.
Speaker 31: holding up a stick like it's a gun and all that right on a public road okay a major highway or now a highway not a major but a highway we got out
my friends
Speaker 31: walk up to him
Speaker 36: and so i said boo you know try to get him in the front or to whist they wouldn't move at all you know you're done there was a photo i said and one guy wanted to poke
Speaker 31: one at me i said better not do that man if you know you could be sued if you're you know guard your guy's eye and and then we all got spooked I was. This is really, really,
really
Speaker 31: We got to get out
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): of here
as
Speaker 47: fast as we
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): can. So we jumped back in the car and went to Montreal for basically a weekend bash, which turned out to be a total
Speaker 9: bust. And so I got a glimpse of the Living Statues Program. This was later applied to the Vietnam War, okay, soon thereafter.
Speaker 9: And the CIA recruited, they just put together a group of 200 special combatants to helicopter into the Ho Chi Minh Trail, into Cambodia and Laos, because it was illegal to fight war then. Each guy, as a loner.
Speaker 9: would uh be dropped off that helicopter he could run like up to four ten you know some endlessly yeah these are really mind control people they would hide behind the tree truck like up to two or three days
to await
Speaker 9: the person there the officer they're supposed to uh shoot you know
Speaker 48: without going
to
Speaker 36: the toilet without batting their eyelashes and
Speaker 36: And in that same frozen pose, and then with some sort of timer they had, I had no idea, the timer would put him awake, warning him that the guy's coming down the road, they'd take a shot at him, kill him, and they'd run like hell. Now, out of that program of 200, there were only 12 survivors, the 30 dozen, we called them.
Speaker 9: They got back to the United States. The army flew them back. They all went to CIA headquarters
Speaker 36: together, and the CIA said, we don't know what the hell you're talking about. You know? We don't know who you are. You know? You're
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): lying. And kicked them out. And they became sort of a motorcycle gang in North Dakota and western Colorado.
And I met
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): one of them, you know? So I knew the back story of this. He was a Canadian Indian.
Speaker 49: Wow. This is
Speaker 50: there at Shia Mahler's facility when he was a kid, when he was young, a teenager.
Do you
Speaker 1: think you know who will win the presidential election or how many seats Democrats or Republicans will win in the House or Senate? Well, there's a legal financial exchange that lets you trade or bet on the outcome of these elections, and it's called Kalshi.
Speaker 1: Kalshi went to court against the Biden administration and won legal approval for election betting for the first time in over 100 years. They have markets on who will win the presidential election, who will control the House and Senate, who will win swing states and more. Kalshi is already being used by hundreds of thousands of people and has facilitated over a billion dollars worth of trades. What's cool about the platform is that you can trade on your opinions to make money or hedge your political risks. You can also check the market odds to see who is more likely to win at any given time. Right now, the odds are near
40.
Speaker 1: $58.42. Not surprisingly, Trump is up big. The election markets are now live to trade. They are the first regulated place where you can do this. Right now, when you sign up at Kalshi.com slash Candace, the first 500 traders who deposit $100 will get a free $20 credit. That's Kalshi.com slash Candace. So I'll tell you what spooks me about what
Speaker 4: you're saying. First and foremost, the more that I have dug into her genealogy, there are a couple of aspects there that
are
Speaker 4: are fitting a little too perfectly with what you're telling me, realizing that her family was involved in the slave trade, that they were involved in Freemasonry, that for whatever reason, she's trying to make everyone believe she's every ethnicity, but what she is, which we have been able to determine from Kamala's family, who have been very forthcoming and don't support what she's doing. Some people in her family have told us, look, we're
Speaker 4: were Syrian Jews. I don't know why she's hiding this fact. And then some of her family members who are Jewish in Canada said the exact same thing. We all feel like she's trying to hide the Jewish aspect, which is quite strange. The other thing that alarms me about what you're saying, though, is for Shmala to engage in this and to engage in what can only be described as program as human torture, to see if you could basically set a human being to blank, set a human being two zero and fill them with whatever you wanted to do, turn them into
Speaker 4: robots. And there is an aspect of Kamala that feels as though she herself has been brainwashed. And I vividly recall her relative who I spoke to saying that far from the depictions of her relationship with her mother that she gives to the public today, her mother was militant is what he said. Her mother was absolutely militant with her children. And she now makes it seem as though she had this flowery childhood.
So
Speaker 4: you have this woman who for work is engaging in this psychiatric torture of citizens from around the world. And then you hear from her family member that she was militant with her
Speaker 39: children. And then I watch Kamala's behavior today and it seems like she is a blank slate in which she allows
everybody.
Speaker 39: Every personality to fill like she can be Jamaican yesterday. She can be Hispanic tomorrow She can act like a black preacher as she's just done and that terrifies me in a sense It's almost as though Kamala herself has been brainwashed. What do you think about that?
Speaker 28: Oh, absolutely. You got to
Speaker 17: understand, you know, her mother had to take care of these patients. They're her treasure. They're, you
Speaker 10: know, that's her ride, you know. That's her income. She was able to buy a house with all that, a pretty damn good house in
Speaker 37: Montreal. But her problem is she couldn't take care of her daughters. She's so much with the patients. So she had to regimen them. And she did, but the techniques that she knew, you
Speaker 24: know. And so, yeah, they were...
Speaker 24: Basically, MKUltra light. Let's say MKUltra light, rather than the whole treatment, okay? And that accounts for weird speech patterns or, you know, or sort of bizarre eye movements and body movements or turkey stuff. That feels straight like these MKUltra guys that you will meet. You know, like that one super soldier I met. You know, he's perfectly normal over a beard, and suddenly he'd go into
Speaker 36: his...
Speaker 36: crazy, jerky fits where it could be dangerous. He could kill you. So, you know, that's basically the same
Speaker 24: as Kamala. Again, she had a lighter version of it. She caught the whole hog. They didn't send her to Syria to kill a bunch of jihadists or anything, but she has definitely been touched by that. And her sister also, she was another one.
Speaker 24: Maya, she was one of the three main campaign advisors to Hillary
Speaker 52: Clinton's presidential campaign. So they
Speaker 17: were placed there sort of as controllers. And look at Hillary, what happened to her, you know,
Speaker 24: from sort of a goofy person into a robotic person. Right. Same thing, the program continued, and her sister was the minder. You know, she had been through the program, and somehow they got Hillary into the program.
Speaker 24: Scary stuff, what they were doing, yeah? - Yeah. - And the scary stuff is, after that program in Montreal and the congressional investigation in the USA by Congress, the whole thing disappeared off the face of the earth. We didn't get these glimmers after that, you know? We know that that big Seattle anti-world trade organization
Speaker 24: uh protest by the labor units and my ex-wife was a member of the culinary workers union in san francisco she was up there she said oh a bunch of these crazy guys from tanada wearing masks there were these small short guys and then the good tall guys came throwing rocks at us you know building rocks at us like crazy guys and the while the tall guys watch and i told her back then
Speaker 24: Oh, those
Speaker 36: are some of the MKUltra patients, and the tall guys are the RCMP, the Royal Canadian Mounted Police, keeping an eye on them.
That's
Speaker 54: just unbelievable, and it's funny that you bring up her sister.
Speaker 36: The program cranked on, but they found, instead of just murdering
Speaker 24: people, probably this Black Lives Matter thing also, you had all these weird...
Speaker 24: Very weird people coming in and starting a lot of trouble, you know, of violence. Oh,
Speaker 56: yeah.
Where
Speaker 24: most of the protesters were served, they're just laid-back hippies, you know?
Speaker 56: Yeah.
So I
Speaker 24: think that was another MK operation, too, especially when the rioting was going on. You know, it was four days of rioting and suddenly burned up plopies, killed
a bunch
Speaker 24: of people. Oh,
Speaker 4: there was no question that that was a fed operation. I mean, when I observed it, it had all of the aspects.
He is. He
Speaker 44: is.
You
Speaker 44: look at Portland, Oregon, and you look at Minneapolis,
Speaker 24: close to the Canadian border, close to the Canadian border for these operatives to come down.
Speaker 4: Wow, fascinating.
And it
Speaker 4: was just amazing. The police just couldn't arrest these people. They just couldn't make it happen. But then January 6th, they're suddenly able to identify every single person who attended this.
Speaker 4: And so you really understood that the government was involved because when they want to capture people, they certainly do. And when they don't, they certainly don't. And it's interesting you bring up her sister, Maya, because very recently I was able to determine how strange it is that her daughter, which is a young woman named Demena Harris, has no father. And what I mean by that, and we just keep seeing what's happened, is that she had a child allegedly when she was a teenager and there's no father on the birth certificate and nobody knows who the father is. And we have been kind of upset
Speaker 4: with on this podcast with this recent recognition that it appears as though they're breeding politicians. They all have this very shady background. Everything you're speaking about reminds me of the Emmanuel Macron upbringing and his story and all the strange aspects. And he's married to a person who lived as a man for 30 years. And their entire state is colluding to gaslight the public on this fact, despite all of the evidence to the contrary, all of the evidence pointing to the fact that Emmanuel Macron is married to a man
Speaker 4: who at best committed statutory rape against him when he was a teenager. And so we're
Speaker 39: seeing this program sort of writ large across society, and it's difficult to communicate to people who are still asleep and who still hold this faith that this process that's happening is above board and democratic and that we're truly a republic and not that there is sort of this hand that is maneuvering behind the scenes
Speaker 39: to elect certain politicians to essentially fulfill their sadistic aims. You're
Speaker 24: absolutely right. It's frank in politics is what it is. You know, we've got a bunch of brain-dead maniacs taking orders, and you wonder what they did to Joe Biden. You know, he's so dependent on his teleprompter and that whatever wire, the wire they've got inside of them, that they seem to be able to take all sorts of people under. As far
Speaker 10: as Maya's,
Speaker 10: kid uh well it's willie brown's a pretty tough guy man so it could be uh you know daddy willie
Speaker 57: wow you know uh
Speaker 10: willie lives
alone in this
Speaker 10: like 20 story 20 story apartment in san francisco
Speaker 24: and uh he likes to pick the food like i said he likes to pick the containers the next successful
A
Speaker 24: black female political hero out of San Francisco, Willie Bell has got to put
Speaker 23: the tap on her.
My
Speaker 59: goodness.
Speaker 23: Oh, good old Uncle Willie. I
do
Speaker 15: want to also ask you, by the way,
Speaker 4: since we're talking about Kamala and her relationships and this kind of open secret, I mean, there really is no other way to say it, but she slept her way to her position of power. It was handed power. This was not a meritocracy in San Francisco. this was,
Speaker 4: whether you were in with the mafia or out with the mafia. But you had mentioned in your piece that Kamala was previously married, and that is rather explosive. You said that she was married to a Canadian Brit and that you remember seeing the marriage
Speaker 60: vividly. Ten
Speaker 61: years ago, I saw the article. I see Kamala in the news. I was taking
Speaker 36: note of it, but I was just reading it on an airplane or something, so I couldn't steal the magazine. you
Speaker 24: know, he's shooting married to
Speaker 24: a Canadian Greek guy, happily married and living in Montreal, you know? And he had some business in Toronto also. Okay. Apparently their house was in Montreal.
Speaker 36: That's all I remember of the thing. It was just something I read and I just had curiosity about. And I'm really regretting I didn't tear the page
Speaker 61: out and stuff in my shirt. You know, I should have done it. Sometimes I'm just too honest. So
it
Speaker 3: must have been a very quick marriage because then she very quickly thereafter married Doug Emhawk.
Speaker 3: yeah
Speaker 61: that's what was that struck me and then emhoff's got daughters and the wife
Speaker 24: is still good and friends of
Speaker 36: kamala and like i say because of the jewish he's uh uh in so-called in film production okay
uh uh uh
Speaker 24: financing film production but he doesn't have a list of films anywhere okay the name's not on any uh billboard so the question
is is is that
Speaker 36: just a cover
Was
Speaker 36: that, you know, San Francisco again? Was that clever?
Speaker 15: Yes. Well, someone did tell me something off record about their relationship.
Speaker 24: If, in fact, you know, she was still married and maybe still married to that Canadian businessman,
Speaker 36: she's probably a Canadian and a British citizen herself, which would make her ineligible to run for
The
Speaker 36: nation's highest office, you know,
Speaker 64: we don't allow Brits to sit in the old world office, basically, not since they burned down the White House.
Speaker 15: Well, we also don't allow Kenyans, but that's taken place in the past before. I, yeah, it really
Speaker 4: is just incredible. Well, I'm going to continue to see if we can find a trace of this.
As I
Speaker 4: said, someone.
The
Speaker 10: secret life of Kamal Harris is fascinating.
Speaker 10: But it's also horrifying because I'm not
Speaker 24: disgusted or a hater or anything. It's just she is just one of the last
Speaker 10: great products of MKUltra. I mean, you know, so that's my interest is clinical. The economy
Speaker 1: has been a major burden on the average American. Wages are flat, expenses are up, and it is very hard to manage to pay all of the bills without using credit cards. If you're a homeowner and you're frustrated with that cycle, I need you to make a 10 minute no obligation call
Speaker 1: today to my friends at American Financing. Interest rates are coming down, and they are now in the low fives. If you're constantly carrying a credit card balance each and every month with a rate in the 20s, American Financing can show you how to put your hard-earned equity to work and get you out of debt. Their salary-based mortgage consultants are saving their customers an average of $800 a month, and if you get started today, you may not even have to make next month's mortgage payment. So call today at 800-795-1210. Again, that's 800-795-1210,
Speaker 1: Or you can visit AmericanFinancing.net slash Owens. Again, that's AmericanFinancing.net slash Owens. And you know, it's funny that you say because realizing
Speaker 4: how effective the MKUltra program has been in creating various mass psychoses and truly you can see how the media is able to just say something and therefore it is true and people get into line. It modifies everyone's behavior to have a woman who never ever made a claim that she was black all throughout her career, you know, and said she was an Indian,
Speaker 4: then suddenly she doesn't even win. They just assert that this is the woman who's going to be the front runner for the Democratic Party. And within two weeks, they're suddenly doing interviews. And she's talking about speaking about her black upbringing and drops a book to that effect. And to see the public just...
or
Speaker 4: at least too large a portion of the public readily accept that is terrifying. There's an element of it that is terrifying, that people do not ordain to think for themselves or to question that narrative. It really shows you really the success of Sigmund Freud and perhaps why they do celebrate him in the textbooks is because he, for the elites, represents their own.
Speaker 4: ability to recognize that it is possible. It is possible to easily persuade the masses with enough insistence about virtually anything. And if we're being convinced about Kamala Harris
Speaker 12: and her black heritage and the struggle that she purports that she lived through when she was a child, then we're ready to be convinced about anything, I would say.
Speaker 65: Yeah.
Speaker 66: And the other weird coincidence is that her
Speaker 36: running mate,
Speaker 36: who is like an unlikely running mate, Tim
Speaker 9: Walz. He's been in Minnesota right there on the Canadian border. And he was involved in counterfeit smuggling of train loads of money from China. He's been in China 30 times.
Speaker 9: Oddly, I never saw him then. I was in East Asia for 25
Speaker 24: years, often went to Beijing, different towns in China, Guangzhou, Beijing, all over the place, and never, I would have seen him sometime then,
Speaker 9: never saw him, you know, and I did a recent story just issued,
Speaker 36: I said, recently about counterfeit.
how
Speaker 36: the counterfeit dollar business went from Britain. Britain shut it down to the EU business, all the other Western. The EU currency, they've created a common currency basically to stop the counterfeiting out of Britain and Holland and the Netherlands, okay? So I talked to a top,
Speaker 36: artist there uh remdan his name is he's a direct descendant of the uh remdan regime the uh great uh world's greatest painter basically interesting fellow and uh after my call they threw him in jail uh but he told me all about the counterfeit
Speaker 24: trail from the netherlands mafia he said we have the world's best engravers
Speaker 9: the british have the best inks
Speaker 9: and paper we have the best engravers you know from that renaissance era era and then the money goes from netherlands to indonesia jakarta and i went there and they said yeah it's uh the the local military government uh purchased
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): all these boeing uh airliners from this very corrupt uh as a representative who used to be the
uh
Speaker 35 (lower-pitched voice): U.S. ambassador to Thailand, pedophile, basically. And from there, the airliners take it to points in
Speaker 36: Asia, and where it then crosses over to the U.S.A., but U.S. is pretty tough on counterfeit. They get detected, so it goes to Canada, and they told me this. This is in Indonesia. Wow. Wow. So this is all part of Waltz's thing, and he's another bizarre figure, too. His father was a psycho, you know, because he was
uh
Speaker 36: in the korean war and had all these nightmares beat his kid beat his wife so uh tim was traumatized and found his shelter his home is uh like uh ultra parentage was uh he felt that the chinese
Speaker 24: communist party is
my dad is
Speaker 24: my mother you know this is what this is how he thought and so he's been a long-term agent and 25 years i never saw him at any of the hangouts or anything like that on the train or plane or anything and so i said that's really really odd he must
Speaker 24: be at one of the party party camps you know you must be so so that's the counterfeit uh the whole counterfeit because i'm very aware because i live down near the mexican border and i've had money seized here everyone here along the border has usually 20 bills in 50s they don't even think the ones but the 20 and 50s everyone has had money coffee there's so much counterfeit down here and this is from the tim waltz
Speaker 24: uh chinese network you know uh undermining the u.s currency so this is
Speaker 69: unbelievable
Speaker 36: it's also a league with the cartel they're all allied with the cartel yes that's why donald trump he
Speaker 37: remember he shut down the chinese uh consulate in
Speaker 36: houston so this whole southwest area is flooded with counterfeit you know and it's really because when
Speaker 10: the bank
in it
Speaker 10: You know, you go to the bank, like Wells Fargo, you say, here's a pack of 20s. I want to deposit this in my account. You know, I got some bills to pay. Tell her, we'll run it through a machine, and then she will, without saying a word, go to the back room, come back out and say, well, your deposit is $180. I said, I gave you $200. She says, you gave me $180 of real money.
Wow. Wow.
that's how
Speaker 10: it goes this is widespread down here there's not a family here who hasn't lost money
Speaker 37: because of counterfeit that's just
Speaker 15: incredible yeah that is really incredible and it's like I said fascinating because it's
Speaker 4: almost the only thing that makes sense when you speak about Kamala Harris and all of these odd aspects of her behavior of the things that she seems to be hiding about her family lineage I mean how much of a psychopath do you have to be to know that you descend from the very people who enslaved
Speaker 4: black Americans, enslaved black Africans, pardon me, in Jamaica. And by the way, brutal. Hamilton Brown was absolutely brutal, really fought for the right to whip them and to be able to abuse them, then intimately involved themselves when the slave trade ended, involved themselves into every layer of government. Then her family was involved in oil, standard oil down in Cuba. And these are
Speaker 4: all the things that once you start looking, you see it's apparent, but to think that this woman can get up there and lie and feel nothing, you know, as she then just takes on the character of somebody who is a descendant of slavery should alarm everyone. It should alarm every single person to know that she lies and feels nothing. Really, to me, only a person who has been through some level of brainwashing, it would be capable of doing this.
Speaker 28: Yeah.
This
Speaker 28: is all possible because you've got to understand the relationship to
Speaker 24: Near Eastern Jews. The Sassoon family, who ran the opium trade in China, turned China into the sick man of Asia. Nearly every Chinese was addicted. Remember that in the late 19th century? And so you have that Near Eastern Jewish element combined with,
Speaker 24: with this Chinese financing of her campaign, okay? And Shanghai, right, you know, I'm very familiar with Shanghai, and unfortunately, I have very, very good media friends in China. One of them died recently, who told me, you know, the Shanghai Party Committee, the most powerful group
Speaker 36: in China, they're
Speaker 71: about third Chinese. They're descendants of Chinese Jews, you know, of the opium, of Sassoon's opium business.
OK,
Speaker 71: so if you've got
Speaker 24: to understand that Chinese build a Jewish connection to control the
Speaker 37: world's money and also to control the world's drugs, that's how you control the money. That's what the Harris-Waltz
Speaker 73: campaign is all
Speaker 66: about.
Speaker 66: Those are the people behind us.
Speaker 3: Wow. Well, I can tell you that this conversation...
Speaker 66: This is not some
Speaker 10: small crime network. This is about global power. And what they're running now
is that
Speaker 10: the United States is the
Speaker 36: sick man of the Americas.
Speaker 74: Yeah, we are.
To
Speaker 36: hell. Just what they did to China to break Chinese power. It was a powerful empire. Very
Speaker 23: wealthy.
That is
Speaker 4: my fear, is that if she gets into power, it is game over, lights off for America. and that's why I wanted to have you
Speaker 4: on the show and to speak about this today. Obviously you've given us so much information and it's going to send us down a million more rabbit holes. It gives me the confidence to know that the stuff that we have uncovered thus far is alarming and that there are, like I said, Americans of every single race and background are realizing that there is something
Speaker 4: that very wrong with the Kamala Harris campaign of every religion was recognizing that there is something very wrong with the Kamala campaign. It has been really a collaborative effort of everyone sending me information and tidbits and saying, hey, I remember this about her. Like I said, even her own family who does not support this communist endeavor is raising alarms here and red flags and telling me things that
Speaker 4: she is saying that are just not true about their family. And so I hope for the people that are listening to this, that it further illuminates you. If you are listening to this, please share this. We obviously are already heading to the polls and it's just important that we can notify as many people about Tim Walz, about Kamala Harris, about her true genealogy, about her true political aims and about her true upbringing as humanly possible. I
Speaker 4: do. Yoishi Clark, I want to thank you so much for joining us today. I appreciate your bravery. I appreciate your willingness to be condemned by the media, which you most certainly will be alongside me. But I believe that it's going to take independent warriors for truth in order for everyone in the world to be awakened to what sorts of evil we are fighting, which I believe is just a small group of elite people who have amassed a lot of control through the media and through these sort of psychiatric programs of brainwash. So Yoishi Clark, thank you so much for joining us.
Speaker 4: joining us today. Yeah,
it's been
Speaker 75: a pleasure. Thanks a lot. I appreciate it.
Speaker 3: Thank you. All right, guys. Well, that is a lot to digest. So many things that I was not even aware
Speaker 4: of myself. So many more things that I now want to learn about to make sure that I am up to
date on
Speaker 4: a lot of the history that has just been blatantly obscured from us all. Like I said, it is so important that we share these videos. If you are watching this right now, please hit the like and the subscribe button on YouTube, hopefully we'll be able to hear
from you
Speaker 4: Yushi Clark in the future. As I said, we want to get as much information out as possible
Speaker 76: before we head to the polls. Thanks for joining us. We will see you guys tomorrow.